househunt.com 2016-12-11

# Privacy Policy - HouseHunt

We at HouseHunt.com, HouseHunt.org and moveUp.com (referred to as "HouseHunt," "we," "us," or "our") recognize the importance of protecting the privacy of certain information ("Information") collected about our users (referred to as "users," "you" or "your"). This privacy statement discloses what information we gather, how we use it, and how to correct or change it. At HouseHunt it is our intention to give you an understanding about how we collect your Information and the use we make of it in the course of our business. 

To that end, HouseHunt gathers two types of information about Users: data that Users provide through optional, voluntary registration on our sites; and data HouseHunt gathers through aggregated tracking, mainly by tallying page views throughout our sites. Such information enables us to tailor our content to fit Users' needs better and to help our service providers understand our Users. We do not share Information with advertisers. Because HouseHunt derives its revenue mainly from e-commerce, providing such aggregated data is essential to keeping our service free to the public. However, be assured that HouseHunt will not disclose personal Information to third parties without your consent, except as may be noted in this Privacy Policy or disclosed to you when the Information is submitted. 

How does HouseHunt collect Information?

Optional registration

We collect information by specifically requesting it from you. Generally this occurs when you register at a site or request information or a service. Usually, the HouseHunt sites and HouseHunt's service partners use your information to operate the sites and to deliver services you request. 

Usage tracking

Use of Internet Protocol ("IP") Addresses: 

An IP address is a unique number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you're surfing the Internet so that your computer can be identified by the main computers, known as "Web servers," that "serve up" Web pages. 

HouseHunt collects IP addresses for the purposes of system administration, and to audit the use of our site. When Users request pages from HouseHunt and/or its affiliates' sites, our servers log the Users' IP addresses. We do not normally link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable, which means that a User's session will be logged, but the User will remain anonymous to us. We can and will use IP addresses to identify a User when we feel it is necessary to protect our service, site, users or others. 

Use Of Cookies

What are cookies? Cookies are small pieces of information that a Web site sends to your computer for record-keeping purposes, which information is stored in a file on your computer. Cookies make Web surfing easier for you by saving your preferences so that we can use the saved information to facilitate your use of our Web site when you return to the site. Cookies do not tell us your individual identity unless you have chosen to provide it to us. We never save passwords or credit card information in cookies. The use of cookies is an industry standard, and as such, you'll find that most major Web sites use them. 

By showing how and when Users access a site, cookies help us see which areas are popular and which are not. Many improvements and updates to the site are based on such data as total number of visitors and pages viewed. This information is most easily tracked with cookies. We use the information from cookies to provide services better tailored to our Users' needs. 

Most cookies expire after a defined period of time, or you can delete your cookie file at any time. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, note that some parts of HouseHunt's services will not function properly or may be considerably slower if you refuse cookies. For example, without cookies, you will not be able to set personalized preferences, and/or may have difficulty completing marketing transactions. 

HouseHunt and/or its affiliates have two primary uses for its cookies. First, we use them to specify a User's preferences. For example, Users can specify keywords across several categories or markets so you don't have to tell us repeatedly about certain features in the home you are seeking. Second, we use cookies to track Users' Web site usage trends and patterns. This helps us understand our Users' needs better and improve areas of HouseHunt's services that our Users find valuable. While both of these activities depend on the use of cookies, you have the option of disabling the cookies via your browser preferences. 

With whom does HouseHunt share Information?

As a general rule HouseHunt will not disclose any specific personal information that you submit to us about you ("Personal Information") in a manner that connects you with the Personal Information, except when we have your permission or under special circumstances, such as when we believe in good faith that the law requires it or under the circumstances described below. The following describes some of the ways that your Personal Information may be disclosed. 

Real Estate Agents: Personal Information is disclosed to our local real estate agents in the geographical area that you request for the purpose of assisting you in a real estate transaction. 

Mortgage Lenders: Personal information may be disclosed to our local mortgage lenders in the geographical area that you request for the purpose of assisting you in a mortgage transaction. 

Third Party & Aggregate Data: From time to time, you may be offered the opportunity to receive materials or special offers from third parties exists. If you opt to receive information from these third parties, HouseHunt will (with your permission) share your name and e-mail address with such third parties. Under confidentiality agreements, HouseHunt may match Personal Information with third party data. Also, HouseHunt may keep track of what portions of the Website Users are visiting and other User statistics, and aggregate this information to help us create a better experience for users of our Web site. This is all done without knowing your name or other Personal Information in order to describe our viewers and services to prospective partners, advertisers, and other third parties, and for other lawful purposes. 

Other: HouseHunt may also disclose account Information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this Information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating HouseHunt's rights, or may be causing injury to or interference (either intentionally or unintentionally) with any of HouseHunt's rights or property, other HouseHunt Users, or anyone else. HouseHunt may disclose or access account Information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it and for administrative and other purposes that we deem necessary to maintain, service, and improve our products and services. 

How can you control the usage of Information?

In case you change your mind or some Personal Information changes (such as your zip code or e-mail address), we will try to provide a way to correct, update or remove the Personal Information that you give us. We also give you the opportunity to control the communications we direct to you. If a User wishes to update Personal Information or objects to any usage provided herein for any reason, he/she may e-mail the requested change to: [support@househunt.com](mailto:support@househunt.com). 

What happens when you link to a third party site?

You should be aware that when you are on HouseHunt's and/or its affiliates' sites you could hyperlink or be directed to other sites that are beyond our control and/or outside our service. For example, if you "click" on a HouseHunt.com search result, the "click" may transfer you off the HouseHunt.com site. These other sites may include sites of advertisers, sponsors and partners unrelated to HouseHunt. These other sites may send their own cookies to Users, collect data, or solicit Information. 

HouseHunt and its affiliates do not control such sites, and, therefore, are not responsible for their contents or the hyperlinks or advertising they choose to place on such sites. HouseHunt's and/or its affiliates' inclusion of hyperlinks to these sites do not imply any endorsement of the material on such sites or any association with their operators. HouseHunt's policy does not extend to anything that is inherent in the operation of the Internet, which is beyond HouseHunt's and its affiliates' control. 

Please keep in mind that whenever you give out information online (for example, via message boards or chat) that information can be collected and used by people you don't know. While HouseHunt and its affiliates strive to protect their Users' information and privacy, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you disclose online, and you disclose such information at your own risk. 

Is my Information secure from others using the HouseHunt site?

The importance of security of all information associated with our Users is an important concern to us. We exercise care in providing secure transmission of your information from your computer to our servers. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your information, HouseHunt and its affiliates can't ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or from our online products or services, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, HouseHunt uses industry standard efforts to safeguard the confidentiality of your information, such as firewalls and Secure Socket Layers. However, "perfect security" does not exist on the Internet. 

YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF THESE TERMS

By using this site, you signify your agreement to HouseHunt's Privacy Policy. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH THIS POLICY, PLEASE DO NOT USE THIS SITE. Your continued use of HouseHunt's and/or its affiliates' sites following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes. 

To what does this Online Privacy Statement apply?

This Online Privacy Statement applies to the personal information that we collect from or about you via this HouseHunt Web site (this "Site"). This Site may contain links to other Web sites, and this Online Privacy Statement does not apply to those sites. If you link to any of those sites, we recommend that you review their privacy policies. If we change our privacy policies or practices, we will also change this Online Privacy Statement. 

What personal and technical information do we collect via this Site?

This Site will collect personal information that you voluntarily provide, such as your name, address, telephone number or e-mail address. This Site may also collect information on your preferences, such as language selection; information on which pages within this Site you visit; and certain technical information regarding your computer and operating systems, such as your Internet protocol address, domain name and system configurations and settings. We will not know who you are unless you tell us. 

Additionally, if this Site is a password-protected site, then (a) once you submit your password and enter, this Site will recognize who you are and will collect all information that you submit, including all electronic instructions (including all transaction information), and (b) any information collected about you from this Site may be associated with other identifying information that we have about you. 

How do we use cookies?

On this Site, we may use cookies or other technology to gather information about Site usage to help us improve the content, usability and functionality of this Site, and to remember your personal settings, such as language selection. This will help us understand how many new and repeat users visit this Site, which features or pages are most popular, and user browsing and usage patterns. 

Additionally, if this Site is a password-protected site, then this Site may use cookies or other technology to help us authenticate you, recognize your user attributes, and facilitate your navigation and entitlements throughout the Site. 

What if you have your browser set with privacy preferences?

This Site may contain information, including P3P privacy policies ("Privacy Preference Information"), intended to work with your selected privacy preferences. While we have tried to make such Privacy Preference Information included within this Site conform to this full-text Online Privacy Statement, this Online Privacy Statement is the definitive statement of privacy policies and practices for this Site. 

How do we use, share and secure personal information that we collect via this Site?

HouseHunt will use, share, secure and otherwise process any personal information that we collect from or about you via this Site only for the purposes stated here. The Information will be shared only with our agents and only for purposes of assisting you in a real estate transaction in the geographical area you select. 

What should you know about e-mail?

We recommend that you not send us any individual personal information via nonsecure methods of communication, including via public electronic communication channels, such as Internet e-mail, which are generally not secure. 

What happens where you close your account?

If you decide to close your account, the Funds will continue to adhere to the privacy policies and practices as described in this notice. 

Whom should you contact if you have questions about this Online Privacy Statement?

If you have any questions regarding this Online Privacy Statement, or our privacy-related practices, please contact us by e-mail at [support@househunt.com](mailto:support@househunt.com) or by phone at (714) 536-3122. You can also contact us by mail at: HouseHunt, Inc., Attention: User Service Dept., Reference: Privacy, 19671 Beach Boulevard Suite 208, Huntington Beach, CA 92648.
